{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Home Safety Assessment \u0026 Disability Planners","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40274/":{"taskOID":40274,"originalTaskOID":40274,"setID":577,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4440,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Disabilities","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of disabilities need to be addressed? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3883,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Mobility/agility (wheelchair, walker)","answerDisplayText":"Mobility/agility (wheelchair, walker)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2945,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Hearing","answerDisplayText":"Hearing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5695,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sight","answerDisplayText":"Sight","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6144,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Strength/range of motion (lifting, reaching, bending)","answerDisplayText":"Strength/range of motion (lifting, reaching, bending)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5570,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Sense of touch/dexterity (turning knobs)","answerDisplayText":"Sense of touch/dexterity (turning knobs)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5817,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Smell","answerDisplayText":"Smell","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1471,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Cognition (dementia, Alzheimer's)","answerDisplayText":"Cognition (dementia, Alzheimer's)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4433,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Residence","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of residence is it?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4393,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One-story single family home","answerDisplayText":"One-story single family home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6565,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two-story single family home","answerDisplayText":"Two-story single family home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6603,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Unit on ground floor of multi-family residence (condo, townhouse, apartment etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Unit on ground floor of multi-family residence (condo, townhouse, apartment etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6604,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Unit on upper floor of multi-family residence (condo, townhhouse, apt., etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Unit on upper floor of multi-family residence (condo, townhhouse, apt., etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5572,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Separate apt./quarters adjacent to family residence","answerDisplayText":"Separate apt./quarters adjacent to family residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501244,"questionDisplayText":"Approximate Budget","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Approximate budget for design services (excluding product costs)","shortQuestionText":"Approximate budget for design services (excluding product costs)","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":200401,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Up to $1000","answerDisplayText":"Up to $1000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200402,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"$1000 - $5000","answerDisplayText":"$1000 - $5000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200403,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"$5000 - $10,000","answerDisplayText":"$5000 - $10,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3915,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than $10,000","answerDisplayText":"More than $10,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200480,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"I don't know","answerDisplayText":"I don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":9,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4440,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Disabilities","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of disabilities need to be addressed? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3883,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Mobility/agility (wheelchair, walker)","answerDisplayText":"Mobility/agility (wheelchair, walker)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2945,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Hearing","answerDisplayText":"Hearing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5695,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sight","answerDisplayText":"Sight","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6144,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Strength/range of motion (lifting, reaching, bending)","answerDisplayText":"Strength/range of motion (lifting, reaching, bending)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5570,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Sense of touch/dexterity (turning knobs)","answerDisplayText":"Sense of touch/dexterity (turning knobs)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5817,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Smell","answerDisplayText":"Smell","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1471,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Cognition (dementia, Alzheimer's)","answerDisplayText":"Cognition (dementia, Alzheimer's)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3883,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Mobility/agility (wheelchair, walker)","answerDisplayText":"Mobility/agility (wheelchair, walker)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2945,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Hearing","answerDisplayText":"Hearing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5695,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sight","answerDisplayText":"Sight","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6144,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Strength/range of motion (lifting, reaching, bending)","answerDisplayText":"Strength/range of motion (lifting, reaching, bending)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5570,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Sense of touch/dexterity (turning knobs)","answerDisplayText":"Sense of touch/dexterity (turning knobs)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5817,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Smell","answerDisplayText":"Smell","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1471,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Cognition (dementia, Alzheimer's)","answerDisplayText":"Cognition (dementia, Alzheimer's)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4433,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Residence","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of residence is it?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4393,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One-story single family home","answerDisplayText":"One-story single family home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6565,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two-story single family home","answerDisplayText":"Two-story single family home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6603,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Unit on ground floor of multi-family residence (condo, townhouse, apartment etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Unit on ground floor of multi-family residence (condo, townhouse, apartment etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6604,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Unit on upper floor of multi-family residence (condo, townhhouse, apt., etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Unit on upper floor of multi-family residence (condo, townhhouse, apt., etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5572,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Separate apt./quarters adjacent to family residence","answerDisplayText":"Separate apt./quarters adjacent to family residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4393,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One-story single family home","answerDisplayText":"One-story single family home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6565,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two-story single family home","answerDisplayText":"Two-story single family home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6603,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Unit on ground floor of multi-family residence (condo, townhouse, apartment etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Unit on ground floor of multi-family residence (condo, townhouse, apartment etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6604,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Unit on upper floor of multi-family residence (condo, townhhouse, apt., etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Unit on upper floor of multi-family residence (condo, townhhouse, apt., etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5572,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Separate apt./quarters adjacent to family residence","answerDisplayText":"Separate apt./quarters adjacent to family residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501244,"questionDisplayText":"Approximate Budget","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Approximate budget for design services (excluding product costs)","shortQuestionText":"Approximate budget for design services (excluding product costs)","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":200401,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Up to $1000","answerDisplayText":"Up to $1000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200402,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"$1000 - $5000","answerDisplayText":"$1000 - $5000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200403,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"$5000 - $10,000","answerDisplayText":"$5000 - $10,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3915,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than $10,000","answerDisplayText":"More than $10,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200480,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"I don't know","answerDisplayText":"I don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":200401,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Up to $1000","answerDisplayText":"Up to $1000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200402,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"$1000 - $5000","answerDisplayText":"$1000 - $5000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200403,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"$5000 - $10,000","answerDisplayText":"$5000 - $10,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3915,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than $10,000","answerDisplayText":"More than $10,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200480,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"I don't know","answerDisplayText":"I don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":9,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40274/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40274,"taskName":"Disability Planner","taskDescription":"Design a Space to Accommodate a Disability","xmTaskDescriptor":"Home Safety Assessment \u0026 Disability Planners","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":294,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Disability bedroom entrance space disabled","textMessagingName":"Plan Disability","rolloverLongDesc":"Specialist who systematically evaluates the existing space in light of the specific disability in question \u0026 then makes recommendations about what changes can best support the independence \u0026 safety of the disabled person. Note separate categories for large scale remodeling to meet the needs of the handicapped \u0026 another category for building or implementing smaller scale adaptations.","rolloverShortDesc":"Specialist in disability planning. Does not build it.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Design a Space to Accommodate a Disability.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Home Safety Assessment \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Disability Planner","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":20,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":3,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Disability Planner","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Disability Planner","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Disability Planner Need","urlName":"Disability-Planner","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Home Safety Assessment Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Disability Planners","searchKeywords":"Disability,bedroom,entrance,space,disabled,handycap,handicap,consultant,designer,accommodate","emcCategoryOid":-12021,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":577,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}